[{"answer": "No, sir.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "If you thought it was just a fight because it was one you knew that Trayvon Martin was planning to start?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Let's take a look at her demeanor.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "The question is, will the jury believe her account?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "No, I don't watch the news.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "And you didn't have any information from the news that this was a racially charged event?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "EANTEL: Yes.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Are you OK this morning?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Is that a question?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "No, I went to sleep.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Did someone talk with you last night about your demeanor in court yesterday?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, actually, I've only met her once but I will tell you, this is a person who did not want to testify.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 86, "question": "What kind of woman is she?", "qSentId": 85}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "It made you think it was racial?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "And that's because he described him as a creepy ass cracker?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "So it was racial, but it was because Trayvon Martin put race in this?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "You don't think that's a racial comment?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "You don't think that creepy ass cracker is a racial comment?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "It's an offensive term.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "I mean, I'm not saying you ever would in polite company, but is it an offensive term?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Well, I think creepy, you know, speaks for itself.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Let's just clear up, what is a creepy ass cracker and what does it actually mean?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "It's a derogatory term used by white people about white people and black people about white people, yes.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Is it a derogatory term -- is it a derogatory term used by black people about white people?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "I would deem it a racist slur, so I mean, it's all where you're from, Piers, and that's been the problem with this whole -- you know, this whole case is that people want to categorize and group certain people or certain races and think that they all have the same thoughts, the same way of speech.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 136, "question": "But as far as you are concerned, from your knowledge of young people and maybe other trials that you've been involved with and so on, it would not be deemed automatically to be a racist slur?", "qSentId": 135}, {"answer": "ACKSON: I don't know about that.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "Do you know about that?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "I think for them once again, they feel like their son is being put on trial as opposed to George Zimmerman.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "How are they dealing with the reality of this trial now?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Yes, I think that it's been clear.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "In terms of the way the legal case is playing out and in particular the evidence of Rachel Jeantel, are you feeling quite confident that you've established now from everything that we've seen and heard in the first few days certainly a clear indication that it looks like George Zimmerman was following Trayvon Martin and that could be significant?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Well, I think that she did take some punches.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "But from a legal prospective, where are we?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Well, definitely is a racial slur.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Do you think it's a -- is it a racial slur?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "That Trayvon got hit -- Trayvon got hit.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "So the last thing you heard was some kind of noise like something hitting somebody?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "No, sir.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "You don't know that, do you?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "No, sir.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 244, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 243}, {"answer": "So was she.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Why is he lying to police?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I was going to say, though, you know, we talked a lot about Stand Your Ground law in this case but I think that she stood her ground and obviously, as she doesn't have perfect testimony, some lies have been pointed out.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "Gloria?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Yes, close.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "So he told you that he could see the man again and the man was behind him, correct?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "Objection, argumentative.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "And if he were hiding somewhere and the man walked close to him, they would be close together, correct?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "He got close to Trayvon, yes, sir.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "In any event, your sense of it was that they got close together at that point?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Same objection, argumentative.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "You're saying that if Trayvon Martin was getting ready to assault this man that he would have said, hang on a minute, I'll call you back?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "If he was going to confront the man, he would have told me, I'm about to confront the man and see what he wants.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "What about that he would have told you if he was getting ready to have a fight?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "The problem is her testimony has evolved over a period of time and she has been discredited somewhat.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Gloria?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Well, I can tell you exactly what was going on.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "How would you assess the temperature of the jury as all this was going down between Rachel Jeantel and Don West?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "Well, fascinating and it doesn't surprise me at all, Piers, because as I looked at her coming into the courtroom, this is the first witness that anybody has seen in this case and she comes in and I'm sorry, she comes in in jeans and a sweater and a little blouse.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "What would you make of that analysis of the -- of the all-female six-woman jury?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Want to jump in, Jo-Ellan?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Well, exactly.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Is this a sign of a problem endemic to the NFL or is it a wider issue about American culture and America's relationship with guns, and the fact that actually crime rate in the NFL and the players is probably not dissimilar to the crime rate outside the NFL?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Well, it tells me about the mindset of Aaron Hernandez if, in fact, this is true.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "What does that tell you about the mindset of some of these players?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Well, my reaction is regret, number one.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "What is your reaction to this?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Well, the White House is a very small place.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "So approval from whom, would you surmise?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "It's not well-informed.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "So your suggestion, obviously, very well-informed suggestion from your background, is the White House would have directed him to do this?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "And that would be from the White House?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "I can't really discuss that program, which as far as I know is still classified.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "First of all, is that true?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "I suppose first legally and second ethically.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Properly in what sense?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130627pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "As far -- in collection of information?", "qSentId": 644}]